<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false"> Movie Catalog </string>
    <string name="movie_title" translatable="false">Movie Title</string>
    <string name="rating" translatable="false">7.0/10</string>
    <string name="movie_desc" translatable="false">Description of Movie</string>
    <string name="language_setting">Language Setting</string>

    <string-array name="menu_catalog">
        <item> Movie </item>
        <item> TV Series </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movies_title" translatable="false">
        <item> Venom </item>
        <item> Aquaman </item>
        <item> "Avenger: Infinity War" </item>
        <item> Bird Box </item>
        <item> Bohemian </item>
        <item> Bumblebee </item>
        <item> Creed II </item>
        <item> Deadpool 2 </item>
        <item> "How To Train You're Dragon" </item>
        <item> Dragon Ball Z </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tv_series_title" translatable="false">
        <item> Fairy Tail </item>
        <item> The Flash </item>
        <item> Game Of Throne </item>
        <item> Gotham </item>
        <item> Iron Fist </item>
        <item> Naruto Shippuden </item>
        <item> N.C.I.S </item>
        <item> Super Girl </item>
        <item> Arrow </item>
        <item> The Walking Dead </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movies_rating" translatable="false">
        <item> 6.6/10 </item>
        <item> 6.8/10 </item>
        <item> 8.3/10 </item>
        <item> 6.9/10 </item>
        <item> 8.0/10 </item>
        <item> 6.5/10 </item>
        <item> 6.8/10 </item>
        <item> 7.5/10 </item>
        <item> 7.7/10 </item>
        <item> 5.6/10 </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tv_series_rating" translatable="false">
        <item> 6.2/10 </item>
        <item> 6.8/10 </item>
        <item> 8.2/10 </item>
        <item> 6.9/10 </item>
        <item> 6.1/10 </item>
        <item> 7.7/10 </item>
        <item> 6.9/10 </item>
        <item> 6.1/10 </item>
        <item> 5.9/10 </item>
        <item> 7.3/10 </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movies_description">
        <item>"Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own."</item>
        <item>"Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm's half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne."</item>
        <item>"the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain."</item>
        <item>"Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety."</item>
        <item>"Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock 'n' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury's increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess."</item>
        <item>"On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug."</item>
        <item>"Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent with ties to his family's past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life."</item>
        <item>"Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys to save a boy's life."</item>
        <item>"As the son of a Viking leader on the cusp of manhood, shy Hiccup Horrendous Haddock III faces a rite of passage: he must kill a dragon to prove his warrior mettle. But after downing a feared dragon, he realizes that he no longer wants to destroy it, and instead befriends the beast – which he names Toothless – much to the chagrin of his warrior father"</item>
        <item>"Five years have passed since the fight with Piccolo Jr., and Goku now has a son, Gohan. The peace is interrupted when an alien named Raditz arrives on Earth in a spacecraft and tracks down Goku, revealing to him that that they are members of a near-extinct warrior race called the Saiyans."</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tv_series_description">
        <item> "Natsu Dragneel and his friends travel to the island Kingdom of Stella, where they will reveal dark secrets, fight the new enemies and once again save the world from destruction." </item>
        <item> "After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to discover he is not the only "meta-human" who was created in the wake of the accelerator explosion — and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it won't be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become…The Flash." </item>
        <item> "even noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Night's Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and icy horrors beyond." </item>
        <item> "Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime world's greatest foes, a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordon's story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to navigate the multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City, the spawning ground of the world's most iconic villains? And what circumstances created them – the larger-than-life personas who would become Catwoman, The Penguin, The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?" </item>
        <item> Danny Rand resurfaces 15 years after being presumed dead. Now, with the power of the Iron Fist, he seeks to reclaim his past and fulfill his destiny. </item>
        <item> "Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.The story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru. After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha, and sets about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy, as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization; Akatsuki." </item>
        <item> "From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position." </item>
        <item> "Twenty-four-year-old Kara Zor-El, who was taken in by the Danvers family when she was 13 after being sent away from Krypton, must learn to embrace her powers after previously hiding them. The Danvers teach her to be careful with her powers, until she has to reveal them during an unexpected disaster, setting her on her journey of heroism." </item>
        <item> "Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow." </item>
        <item> "Sheriff's deputy Rick Grimes awakens from a coma to find a post-apocalyptic world dominated by flesh-eating zombies. He sets out to find his family and encounters many other survivors along the way." </item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="movies_image">
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
    </array>

    <array name="tv_series_image">
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_god</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_iron_fist</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ncis</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_supergirl</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_walking_dead</item>
    </array>

</resources>
